const questions = [
    {
      question:
        "What year was BC founded?",
      answers: ["1859", "1863", "1867", "1872"],
      correct: "1863",
      location: 0 // Devlin Hall
    },
    {
        question:
          "What is the statue of outside Higgins?",
        answers: ["St. Aloysius Gonzaga", "St. Francis", "St. Ignatius of Loyola",  "St. Peter Faber"],
        correct: "St. Ignatius of Loyola",
        location: 1 // Higgins Hall
      },
      {
        question:
          "What school is located in Fulton?",
        answers: ["Carroll School of Management", "Connell School of Nursing", "Lynch School of Education", "Morrissey College of Arts and Sciences"],
        correct: "Carroll School of Management",
        location: 2 // Fulton Hall
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the second floor?",
        answers: ["Carney Hall", "Eagle’s Nest", "Hillside Dining Hall", "Stuarts Dining Hall"],
        correct: "Eagle’s Nest",
        location: 3 // Mcelory Commons
      },
      {
        question:
          "What play is represented on the bottom right corner of the tinted window?",
        answers: ["Antony & Cleopatra", "Hamlet", "Julius Caesar", "King Lear"],
        correct: "Hamlet",
        location: 4 // Baptist Library
      },
      {
        question:
          "How many floors are there in O'neill Library?",
        answers: ["4 floors", "4.5 floors", "5 floors", "6 floors"],
        correct: "5 floors",
        location: 5 // O’neill Library
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which floor is Connell school of Nursing located in Maloney Hall?",
        answers: ["2nd floor", "3rd floor", "4th floor", "5th floor"],
        correct: "2nd floor",
        location: 6 // Maloney Hall
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the black box theatre located in Robsham Theatre?",
        answers: ["Bonn Studio Theatre", "Lobo’s Theatre", "Margot Connell Theatre", "Watts Theatre"],
        correct: "Bonn Studio Theatre",
        location: 7 // Robsham Theatre
      },
      {
        question:
          "Where is the swimming pool located?",
        answers: ["1st Floor", "2nd Floor", "3rd Floor", "4th Floor"],
        correct: "1st Floor",
        location: 8 // Margot Connell Recreation Center
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who is the statue of in front of Alumni Stadium?",
        answers: ["Doug Flutie", "John Johnson", "Luke Kuechly", "Matt Ryan"],
        correct: "Doug Flutie",
        location: 9 // Alumni Stadium/Conte Forum
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the room number of the biggest lecture hall in Merkert?",
        answers: ["127", "130", "133", "136"],
        correct: "127",
        location: 10 // Merkert Chemistry Center
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the cafe bar in Stokes?",
        answers: ["The Caramel Bar", "The Chocolate Bar", "The Hazelnut Bar", "The Vanilla Bar"],
        correct: "The Chocolate Bar",
        location: 11 // Stokes Hall
      }
  ];

  export default questions;
